Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Evans, Don
    - The Trials and Tribulations of Staggerlee Booker T. Brown
      - Crossroads Theatre, New Brunswick, N.J.
        - Royalty statements, 1983
      - Karamu House, Cleveland, Ohio, 1984-1985
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983-1986
      - Trenton Theatre Guild, Princeton, N.J., 1983-1984
  - Ewald, Carl, 1962-1966, undated
  - Ewen, David, 1969-1971, undated
  - Eythe, William, 1948-1949, undated
  - Fairchild, Margaret
    - Contracts, 1963-1968
    - Correspondence, 1962-1969
    - Notes, 1963-1969, undated
    - Photograph, undated
    - Printed matter, 1961-1969
  - Fairlie, Gerard
    - Bulldog Drummond series
      - Contracts, 1939, 1949-1953
      - Correspondence
        - 1948-1949
        - 1950-1955, (4 folders) (Box 125)
      - Miscellany, 1952-1954, undated
      - Notes, 1948-1955, undated
    - Lumberjack, 1953-1954
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and notes, 1948-1953, undated
    - No Sleep for McCall, 1954-1955
    - The Return of the Black Gang, 1954-1955
    - Winner Takes All
      - Correspondence, 1952-1953
      - Miscellany, 1952-1953, undated
    - With Prejudice, 1951-1952
  - Falb, Lewis W., 1981, undated
  - Farber, Myron
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1976-1978, 1984
    - New York Times articles, 1977-1985, undated, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Somebody Is Lying
      - Contracts, 1976-1985, 1994
      - Correspondence, 1977-1985, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1977-1986, 1994, undated, (3 folders)
      - Page proofs, 1982
      - Printed matter, 1978-1985, undated, (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Royalty statements, 1979-1985
    - The World of the Von Bulows
      - Contracts, 1983
      - Correspondence, 1982-1985, undated
      - Notes, 1982-1985, undated
      - Printed matter, 1982-1985, undated
      - Proposals, undated
  - Farmer, Frances
    - Booking record, 1958
    - Contracts, 1957
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958
    - Notes, 1957-1958, undated
    - Photographs, 1958, undated
    - Printed matter, 1958-1959
  - Fargason, John T.
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973
    - Notes, 1970-1973, undated
  - Farrow, John C.
    - Contracts, 1971
    - Correspondence, 1971-1976, 1986
    - Notes, 1971-1976, undated (Box 128)
    - Royalty statements, 1971-1974
  - Farwell, Jonathan
    - Contracts, 1961-1968
    - Correspondence, 1961-1969, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1962-1965, undated
    - Photographs, undated
    - Printed matter, 1961-1968, undated
  - Feifel, Herman, 1965-1967, 1973-1978, undated
  - Feiler, Jesse I.
    - Away! 1966-1967
    - The Little Saint
      - Contracts, 1966
      - Correspondence, 1965-1973
      - Notes, 1966, undated
      - Printed matter, 1964-1968, undated
    - Quintet in A Flat, 1973-1981, undated
    - The Scene Is a Neighborhood, 1965-1966, undated
  - Feldman, Jonathan Marc, 1976
  - Feldman, Walter (Box 129)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975
    - Miscellany, 1973-1975, undated
  - Ferber, Edna
    - Cimarron
      - Contracts, 1930, 1958, 1976-1978
      - Correspondence, 1976-1978
      - Notes, 1969, 1976-1980, undated
    - Come and Get It, 1969, 1977
    - Giant
      - Contracts, 1976-1981, (4 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1983, undated, (3 folders)
      - Notes, 1975-1983, undated (Box 130)
      - Printed matter, 1969, 1978, undated
    - Great Son, 1969, 1976-1979
    - Ice Palace, 1977-1983, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1951, 1976-1977
      - Correspondence, 1974-1983, (3 folders)
      - Notes, 1974-1983, undated
      - Printed matter, 1974-1982
      - Reports, 1969-1977, undated, (2 folders)
      - Royalty statements, 1976-1980
    - The Royal Family, 1975-1977, undated (Box 131)
    - Saratoga Trunk
      - Contracts, 1967, 1976-1977
      - Correspondence, 1975-1982
      - Notes, 1969, 1976-1982, undated
    - Show Boat, 1969, 1975-1979
    - So Big, 1969, 1975-1977, 1983
  - Ferrer, Leticia, 1964-1968, undated
  - Fiddy, Roland, 1970-1971
  - Field, Marjorie
    - Contracts, 1967
    - Correspondence, 1966-1992, (4 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1966-1967, undated
    - Notes, 1967-1968, 1974, 1992, undated, (3 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1966-1978, 1992, undated, (4 folders) (Box 132)
  - Fields, Dorothy
    - Ain't Misbehavin', 1978, undated
    - Annie Get Your Gun
      - Film and television rights
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1979-1995, (5 folders)
        - Notes
          - 1979, (2 folders)
          - 1980-1994, undated (Box 133)
        - Printed matter, 1979, 1987, 1993-1994, undated
      - Foreign productions
        - Amateur and stock rights, 1985-1994, undated, (7 folders)
        - British Isles tour, 1987
        - England (Box 134)
          - Aldwich Theatre, London, England
            - Contracts and correspondence, 1986
            - Notes, 1986
            - Photographs and printed matter, 1986
            - Royalty statements, 1986
          - Chichester Festival Theatre, Chichester, England
            - Contracts and correspondence, 1985-1986, undated
            - Notes, 1985-1986, undated
            - Photographs and printed matter, 1986, undated
            - Royalty statements, 1986
          - Theatre Royal, Plymouth, England
            - Contracts and correspondence, 1986
            - Miscellany, 1986
            - Royalty statements, 1986
        - European tour, 1991-1992, undated, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1974, 1987-1993, undated (Box 135)
        - United Kingdom tour
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1991-1993, (5 folders)
          - Notes, 1986, undated
          - Printed matter, 1992, undated
          - Royalty statements, 1992-1993, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1966-1974, 1982-1996, (2 folders)
        - EMI Classics, 1989-1993 (Box 136)
        - Notes, 1966-1972, 1980-1989, undated
        - Printed matter, 1966, 1983, 1992-1994, undated
      - National tour (1986)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1986
        - Notes and printed matter, 1986, undated
        - Photograph, undated
      - National tour (1991)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1989-1994, undated, (3 folders)
        - Notes, 1990-1993, undated
        - Photographs and printed matter, 1987-1993, undated
        - Promotional packet, 1992
        - Script, 1992
      - Paper Mill Playhouse, Milltown, N.J., 1987
      - Score, undated (Box 137)
      - Script, undated
    - Blackbirds, 1971
    - By the Beautiful Sea, 1953-1954, 1964-1968, 1975, undated
    - Eleanor
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1969-1970, undated
      - Notes, 1968-1971, undated, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1969-1970
    - The Happy Time and Keep It in the Family
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1966-1967
      - Notes and printed matter, 1966-1967, undated
    - Jerome Robbins' Broadway, 1989
    - Kern, Jerome, collaboration project
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990, undated
      - Music, 1935-1940, 1951-1959, 1975, 1991, undated
      - Notes, 1989-1990, undated (Box 138)
    - A Lady Needs a Change
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1978-1979, undated
      - Miscellany, 1978, undated
      - Notes, 1978-1979, undated, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1978-1979, undated
    - Mexican Hayride, 1977
    - Miscellany
      - Awards and honors, 1970-1975, undated
      - Biographical material, 1966-1974, 1993, undated
      - Correspondence, 1964-1994, undated, (4 folders)
      - Lists of collaborators and songs, 1981, 1989, undated
      - Notes, 1964-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 139)
      - Photograph, 1969
      - Representation agreements, 1965-1966, 1974-1975, 1994, undated
    - Mr. Smith Goes to Washington
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1971, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1971
    - “On the Sunny Side of the Street,” 1970-1972, undated
    - Pin-Ups, 1973-1974, undated
    - Redhead
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1958-1974, 1980, 1993, undated
      - Financial records, 1959-1962, 1970
      - Notes, 1967-1973, 1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1958-1959, undated
      - Script, undated
    - Seesaw (Box 140)
      - Amateur and stock rights, 1975-1994, undated, (2 folders)
      - Film negotiations
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1965, 1975-1981, (5 folders)
        - Notes, 1975-1980, undated, (2 folders)
      - Fisher Theatre, Detroit, Mich.
        - Financial records, 1973
        - Printed matter, 1973
      - Foreign productions (Box 141)
        - Amateur and stock rights, 1976-1992, undated, (2 folders)
        - The Royal Theatre, Northampton, England, 1987, undated
      - Mark Hellinger Theatre and Uris Theatre, New York, N.Y.
        - Box office receipts, 1973-1974, (3 folders)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1971-1974, undated, (2 folders)
        - House seats, 1973, undated
        - Miscellany, 1972-1973, undated (Box 142)
        - Notes, 1968-1988, undated, (4 folders)
        - Printed matter, 1972-1974, undated
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1968-1975, 1994-1995
        - Financial records, 1973-1974, undated
      - National tour
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1974
        - Miscellany, 1973-1975
        - Notes, 1974
        - Printed matter, 1974, undated
        - Royalty statements, 1974
      - Recording, 1972-1973, undated
      - Road show
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1974-1975
        - Miscellany, 1974-1975, undated
      - St. Louis Municipal Opera, St. Louis, Mo., 1973
      - Script, 1973
    - Something for the Boys, 1942-1943, 1980-1986 (Box 143)
    - Sugar Babies
      - Correspondence, 1979-1980, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1979-1980, undated
    - Sweet Charity
      - Film
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1965-1969
        - Financial records, 1967-1969
        - Notes, 1965-1969, undated
        - Printed matter, 1965-1969, undated
      - Miscellany, 1987
      - Play
        - Amateur and stock rights
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1966-1969, 1979-1993
          - Notes, 1966-1967, 1979, 1984, undated
          - Royalty statements
            - 1967-1969, 1980-1989, (2 folders)
            - 1990-1994 (Box 144)
        - Caesar's Palace, Las Vegas, Nev.
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1966-1967
          - Notes and printed matter, 1966-1967, undated
        - Foreign productions
          - Australia, 1965-1968, undated
          - France, 1970
          - Great Britain
            - Miscellany, 1970, 1978-1993
            - Prince of Wales Theatre, London, England
              - Contracts and correspondence, 1965-1968
              - Financial records, 1967-1968
              - Notes and printed matter, 1966-1967, undated
              - Photograph, undated
        - Minskoff Theatre, New York, N.Y.
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1985-1987
          - Financial records, 1986-1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 145)
          - Notes, 1985-1987, undated
          - Printed matter, 1986-1987, undated
        - Miscellany (Box 146)
          - Award, 1966
          - Columbia Records, 1965-1969
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1964-1966, 1979-1980, 1993, undated, (2 folders)
          - EMI America Records, 1986, undated
          - Financial records, 1965-1968
          - Notes, 1964-1966, 1994, undated
          - Printed matter, 1964-1968, undated
          - Random House, 1966-1973, 1992-1994
        - National tour (1967)
          - Box office receipts, 1967-1968
          - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 147)
          - Notes and printed matter, 1967, undated
        - National tour (1987)
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1985-1989
          - Financial records, 1987
          - Notes, 1985-1989, undated
          - Printed matter, 1987, undated
        - Palace Theatre, New York, N.Y.
          - Financial records
            - Box office receipts
              - 1966, (3 folders)
              - 1967, (2 folders) (Box 148)
            - Royalty statements, 1966-1967, (2 folders)
          - Printed matter, 1965-1967, undated
        - Pre-Broadway tryouts (1965)
          - Correspondence, 1965-1966
          - Financial records, 1966
          - Notes and printed matter, 1965
        - Pre-Broadway tryouts (1985)
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1985-1986
          - Financial records
            - Box office receipts, 1985, (2 folders)
          - Royalty statements, 1985-1986, undated (Box 149)
          - Notes, 1982-1988, undated
          - Printed matter, 1985, undated
    - “That Show,” 1969
    - A Tree Grows in Brooklyn
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1952, 1967-1982, 1988-1996, undated, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1971, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1966-1982, 1988-1989, undated
      - Script, n.d (Box 150)
    - Up in Central Park, 1967, 1975, 1980
    - “Where There Is Love, There Is Hope,” 1968
    - The Village Idiot
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1967-1968, undated
      - Notes, 1967-1968
    - The Women, 1964-1966
  - Fields, Herbert
    - America's Sweetheart, 1988, 1994
    - Biographical material, undated
    - A Connecticut Yankee
      - Maine State Music Theatre, Brunswick, Maine
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1988-1992
        - Notes and printed matter, 1991
      - Script, 1991
    - Du Barry Was a Lady
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1941, 1971-1974, 1981
      - Notes and printed matter, 1972-1974, 1981, undated
    - Fifty Million Frenchmen, 1974
    - Hit the Deck
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1991-1992
      - Notes and printed matter, 1977, undated
      - Prompt book, undated
    - Panama Hattie (Box 151)
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1972-1978, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes and printed matter, 1973-1976, undated
    - Pardon My English, 1990
  - Fieve, Katia, 1987, undated
  - Filling, Gwyned
    - Contracts, 1948
    - Correspondence, 1948-1949
    - Miscellany, 1948, undated
  - Fink, Kenneth, 1991, undated
  - Finkelstein, Levanna, 1975, undated
  - Fischer, Madelyn, 1963, undated
  - Fish, Robert L., 1978, undated
  - Fisher, Laura, 1994-1998, undated
  - Fitts, Dudley, and Robert Fitzgerald See also Container 39, Breuer, Lee
    - Alcestis, 1985-1987
    - Antigone
      - Contracts, 1968-1971, 1983
      - Correspondence, 1958-1971, 1980-1989
      - Notes, 1958-1962, 1970-1971, 1980, undated (Box 152)
      - Printed matter, 1958-1963, 1970-1971, 1984
      - Royalty statements, 1962-1971, 1984
    - The Birds, 1965-1966, 1978-1979
    - The Frogs, 1964
    - Ladies' Day, 1958-1965
    - Lysistrata
      - Contracts, 1957-1959, 1965-1968, 1978
      - Correspondence, 1958-1969, 1979, 1990
      - Notes, 1958-1962, 1969, 1979, undated
      - Printed matter, 1957-1958, 1978-1979, undated See also Oversize
      - Royalty statements, 1959-1968
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1959-1968, 1984-1985
      - Notes, 1985, undated
      - Printed matter, 1958-1962, 1984-1985, undated
    - The Oedipus Cycle
      - Contracts, 1958-1963, 1977-1980
      - Correspondence, 1958-1968, 1977-1988
      - Miscellany, 1960-1961, 1979-1982, undated
  - Flack, Stuart, 1986
  - Fleischman, Maxine, 1963-1964
  - Flier, Jeffrey S., 1979-1984, undated
  - Flowers, Charles
    - It Never Rains in Los Angeles
      - Contracts, 1970-1971
      - Correspondence
        - 1969
        - 1970-1976, undated, (3 folders) (Box 153)
      - Notes, 1970-1976, undated
      - Page proofs, 1970
      - Printed matter, 1970-1973
      - Royalty statements, 1971-1983
      - Typescript, 1970
    - Laguna, 1970-1973 (Box 154)
    - Miscellany, 1970-1971, undated
    - Proposals, 1970-1974
    - Sex in the Garden of Allah, 1970
    - When Galahad Grows Old, 1970-1972
  - Flynn, John Edward, 1981
  - Foote, Barbara Hallie, 1969, 1977-1979, 1995, undated
  - Foote, Horton
    - 1918 See also Container 174, The Orphans' Home Cycle
      - American Conservatory Theatre, San Francisco, Calif.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1990-1991
        - Financial records, 1991
        - Miscellany, 1991
      - Davidson College Theatre, Davidson, N.C., 1988
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1979-1987
        - Notes, 1979-1984, undated
        - Photographs, 1984
        - Printed matter, 1979-1989
      - Scripts
        - 1979
        - 1981-1983, (3 folders) (Box 155)
      - Shooting schedule, 1984
    - All the Way Home, 1962
    - Alone, undated
    - “American Playhouse”
      - “Keeping On”
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1979-1982
        - Miscellany, 1979-1983, undated
      - “Story of a Marriage,” 1987
    - April Morning
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1970-1972
      - Notes, 1970-1973, undated (Box 156)
      - Script, 1971
    - As Summers Die, 1980
    - Baby, the Rain Must Fall See also Containers 180-181, The Traveling Lady
      - Book, 1964-1971
      - Film
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1963-1971, 1985
        - Financial records, 1967-1971, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1964-1967
        - Notes, 1964-1967
        - Script, 1963
    - Barn Burning, 1978-1980
    - Bessie Smith, 1974, 1986-1989
    - Bill W., 1976 (Box 157)
    - Blind Date, 1981-1988 See also Container 165, Harrison, Texas
    - The Bridge at San Luis Rey, 1957
    - Brother to a Dragonfly, 1978
    - Bus Stop, 1976
    - “Carnival”
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1956
      - Notes, 1956
    - Celebration, 1948, 1961
    - The Chase
      - Book
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1954-1966, 1984-1986, (2 folders)
        - Foreign publications
          - Contracts and correspondence, 1955-1973, (2 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1959, 1965-1966, undated (Box 158)
        - Notes, 1954-1963, 1984, undated
        - Page proofs, 1956
        - Printed matter, 1954-1956
        - Royalty statements, 1956-1972
      - Film
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1953-1966, 1976, (2 folders)
        - Notes, 1965-1969
        - Printed matter, 1957-1966, undated, (2 folders)
        - Profit participation, 1966-1973, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box 159)
        - Correspondence, 1952-1964
        - Notes, 1953-1964, undated
      - Play
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1949-1964
        - Foreign productions
          - Miscellany, 1952-1953, 1968
          - West Germany
            - Contracts and correspondence, 1959-1961
            - Notes, 1959-1961, undated
            - Printed matter, 1961, undated See also Oversize
        - Miscellany, 1950-1958, undated
        - Photographs, 1952 See also Oversize
        - Printed matter, 1952-1953, undated See also Oversize
        - Script, undated
    - The Children of Pride
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1975-1976
      - Notes, 1975-1977, undated
      - Script, 1975 (Box 160)
    - A Christmas Story, undated
    - Claudelle Inglish
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1958-1961
      - Miscellany, 1958-1961, undated
      - Scripts, 1959-1960, (2 folders)
    - Comrades, 1982, undated
    - Convicts See also Container 174, The Orphans' Home cycle
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1984-1991, undated
      - Miscellany, 1977-1979, 1988-1991, undated
      - Scripts, 1979-1987, (2 folders) (Box 161)
    - Courtship See also Container 174, The Orphans' Home cycle and Container 184, Valentine's Day
      - Actors Theatre of Louisville, Louisville, Ky., 1983-1984
      - H.B. Playwrights Foundation, 1978
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1979-1985, undated
        - Notes and printed matter, 1978-1984, undated
      - Script, undated
      - Stage #1, Dallas, Tex., 1983-1985
    - Cousins and The Death of Papa See also Container 174, The Orphans' Home cycle
      - Galley proofs, 1988
      - Miscellany, 1984-1989
      - Script, undated
    - The Dancers
      - Contracts and correspondence
        - 1954-1963
        - 1964-1965, 1987-1990 (Box 162)
      - Miscellany, 1955-1963, 1984-1987, undated
      - Page proofs, 1955
      - Script, 1954
    - The Days of Violence (formerly titled, The Red Headed Lady )
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1964-1970
      - Notes, 1969-1970
    - The Dearest of Friends, 1983-1984, undated See also Containers 175-176, The Roads to Home
    - A Death in the Family, 1961
    - The Death of the Old Man, 1953, 1962-1963, 1978
    - The Displaced Person
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1975-1981
      - Miscellany, 1975-1980
    - Dividing the Estate
      - Great Lakes Theater Festival, Cleveland, Ohio
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1989-1991
        - Miscellany, 1990-1991, undated
      - John Marshall High School, San Antonio, Tex., 1994
      - McCarter Theatre, Princeton, N.J. (Box 163)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1989
        - Miscellany, 1989, undated
      - Miscellany
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1989-1992
        - Notes, 1989-1992, undated
      - Scripts, 1990, undated, (3 folders)
    - “DuPont Show of the Month”
      - The Night of the Storm, 1961
      - “The Gambling Heart,” 1963
    - Fools' Parade, 1969
    - Getting Frankie Married and Afterwards, 1991-1992
    - Gone with the Wind, 1971-1972 (Box 164)
    - “Goodyear Television Playhouse,” “Expectant Relations,” 1953
    - The Habitation of Dragons
      - Miscellany
        - Correspondence, 1960, 1987-1992, undated
        - Notes, 1960, 1986-1989, undated
      - Pittsburgh Public Theatre, Pittsburgh, Pa.
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1986-1988
        - Financial records, 1988
        - Miscellany, 1986-1988
        - Notes, 1985-1988, undated
        - Printed matter, 1988 (Box 165)
        - Scripts, 1962, 1988-1989, (4 folders)
    - Harrison, Texas, 1985 See also Container 157, Blind Date; Container 174, The One-Armed Man; and Container 175, The Prisoner's Song
    - Home Movie, 1971
    - In My Beginning, undated
    - The Indian Fighters, 1957-1963
    - The King Makers (alternate title The Governor's Lady ), undated, (2 folders) (Box 166)
    - “Lamp Unto My Feet,” “Ludie Brooks,” 1955
    - Land of the Astronauts, 1987-1988
    - Laura Dennis, 1995, undated
    - Lily Dale See also Container 174, The Orphans' Home cycle
      - J.R. Productions
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1984-1987
        - Miscellany, 1984-1986
        - Notes, 1982-1986
        - Printed matter, 1986-1987
        - Royalty statements, 1986-1987, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box 167)
        - Contracts and correspondence, 1982-1996
        - Notes, 1985-1991, undated
      - Script, undated
    - Lyndon, 1974
    - Man of Manifest Destiny, 1959
    - The Man of the House, 1994, undated
    - The Man Who Climbed the Pecan Trees, 1988, undated
    - Marcus Strachen, 1948, undated
    - Mark Twain, undated
    - Midnight Caller and John Turner Davis, 1958
    - Miscellany (Box 168)
      - Awards and honors
        - Alley Award, 1991
        - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1995
        - The Ensemble Studio Theatre Gala, New York, N.Y., 1985
        - Other awards, 1986-1996, undated
        - The William Inge Festival, Independence, Kans., 1989
        - Writers Guild of America West, Screen Laurel Award, 1993
      - Biographical material
        - Fact sheets, 1945-1992, undated
        - Printed matter, 1952-1995, undated
      - Contracts and correspondence
        - 1946-1985, (4 folders)
        - 1986-1996, (3 folders) (Box 169)
      - Family papers
        - Guide to Horton Foote collection (not at Library of Congress), 1985
        - Various family members, 1973, 1980-1984, 1994, undated
      - Financial records
        - Royalty statements
          - Harrison, Texas: Eight Television Plays, 1956-1987
          - Three Plays, 1962-1985
        - Various expenses and statements, 1958, 1974-1992 (Box 170)